socialmediafeed.me 2019-06-08

# Privacy Policy | SocialMediaFeed.me | View Latest Social Media Feed from Instagram Popular People Online

##### SocialMediaFeed.me Privacy Policy

* * *

######  SocialMediaFeed.me operates several websites including SocialMediaFeed.me.  
It is SocialMediaFeed.me policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our websites. 

###### Website Visitors

Like most website operators, SocialMediaFeed.me collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. SocialMediaFeed.me purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how SocialMediaFeed.me visitors use its website. From time to time, SocialMediaFeed.me may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.

###### Instagram Content

All photographic and video content on SocialMediaFeed.me comes from Instagram and was publicly available at the time of its appearing on our site. The content is owned by those who posted it and carries the copyright attributed by that owner. You can control your content's visibility by changing your Instagram settings to prevent your content from appearing on third-party sites like SocialMediaFeed.me. Visit Instagram's help center to learn more about [controlling your visibility](https://help.instagram.com/116024195217477/).

If you would like to prevent your profile from appearing specifically on SocialMediaFeed.me, please open the Submit Profile Removal Request

###### Aggregated Statistics

SocialMediaFeed.me may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. SocialMediaFeed.me may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, SocialMediaFeed.me does not disclose personally-identifying information.

###### Cookies

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor's computer, and that the visitor's browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. SocialMediaFeed.me uses cookies to help SocialMediaFeed.me identify and track visitors, their usage of SocialMediaFeed.me website, and their website access preferences. SocialMediaFeed.me visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using SocialMediaFeed.me websites, with the drawback that certain features of SocialMediaFeed.me websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

###### Ads

Ads appearing on any of our websites may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by SocialMediaFeed.me and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

###### Privacy Policy Changes

Although most changes are likely to be minor, SocialMediaFeed.me may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in SocialMediaFeed.me sole discretion. SocialMediaFeed.me encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy.
